It was a situation there where everybody was happy...
当时大家都很高兴
...to see the war coming to an end...
看到战争接近尾声
...and the Germans didn't really have a heart for it.
而德军也无心作战
They realized that the end was there.
他们也感到战争将结束
We'd say the only good Kraut is a dead one.
我以前说过 唯一的好德军是死掉的德军
But there was something in there that you know, hey that was a kid.
可是后来发现他们只是些孩子
Most of them were kids. We all were kids.
大部分还只是孩子 我们都还是孩子
They had a job to do the same way as me.
他们要做的工作跟我一样
So, we went about and did the job that we had to do.
所以我们去把该做的工作做好
I think we thought that the Germans...
我想我们以为德国人
...were probably the evilest people in the world.
也许是世上最邪恶的人
But...
但是...
...as the war went along...
当战争持续进行下去
...we found out also that it wasn't the Germans, per se.
我们也发现并不是德国人本身的问题
A lot of those soldiers...
很多...他们的士兵
I've thought about this often.
我常常这么想
That man and I might've been friends.
有些人可能可以成为好友
We might have had a lot in common.
我们可能有很多共同之处
He might have liked to fish, you know.
你知道 他也许喜欢钓鱼
He might have liked to hunt.
他也许喜欢打猎
You never know, you know.
这很难说的
They were doing what they were supposed to do.
当然 他们只是在尽职做事
And I was trying to do what I was supposed to do.
而我也只是在做我该做的事
But, under different circumstances...
可是在不同的情境下
...we might have been good friends.
我们可能成为好朋友
That way.
那边
Tell you one thing about the Krauts:
我告诉你德国人的一个特色
They sure clean up good.
他们真会清理东西
Yeah, all you need's a little Mozart.
是啊 只需要给他们一点莫扎特就行了
Beethoven.
贝多芬
Sorry, sir?
你说什么 长官?
That's not Mozart.
那不是莫扎特
That's Beethoven.
那是贝多芬
Come on, chicken.
快过来 鸡崽
All right, this one's got some, George.
有了 这只有一些 乔治
You...
你...
You grab the chicken and I'm gonna grab the eggs.
你抓住鸡 我来拿蛋
Great, all right.
好 没问题
Just grab him by the foot.
你抓住它的脚
Come on, chicken.
快过来 鸡崽
All right, If this thing bites me...
好吧 如果它咬我的话...
...Frank, I swear I'll shoot it.
法兰克 我发誓我会毙了他
Guten Tag, Fraulein.
嗨 你好吗?
Guten Tag.
你好...
Hold on! Hold...
等一下!
But, George...
喂 乔治
I'll be right back.
我马上就回来
Hold on a second, hold on.
等我一下
Hey, hey, come on.
嘿 别这样
I just wanna talk to you.
我只是想和你说说话
Okay, look what I got. Chocolate bar?
看我有什么? 巧克力棒?
You like that? You like chocolate?
你喜欢吗? 你喜欢巧克力吗?
Hey, Luz, why don't you leave her alone?
鲁兹 你别去烦她好吗?
Frank, why don't you just leave me alone, okay?
法兰克 你别来烦我好吗?
You don't like chocolate?
你不喜欢巧克力吗?
I don't like it either.
算了 我也不喜欢巧克力
How about this? Cigarettes.
那这个呢? 香烟
Camel?
骆驼牌的
Yeah, you like that?
你喜欢这个 对不对?
Come on, Luz.
够了 鲁兹
Frank, please, why don't you go make your omelet?
法兰克 拜托你去弄你的炒蛋好吗?
Well, you ain't getting none of my eggs, blockhead.
我一点蛋都不会分给你的 你这个笨蛋
Jesus, my friend just keeps talking.
老天 我朋友真爱说话
Here, I got two packs here.
拿去 我有两包
Give it to your friends or something.
拿给你的朋友之类的
Why don't you come and sit down?
你干吗不过来坐下?
Wanna sit down?
要不要坐下来?
Here?
这里?
Come on, that's it.
来吧 就是这样
Hey, Frank, hold on.
法兰克! 等等...
Perc, Jesus, come on.
派康提! 别这样
What?
怎么啦?
That Captain Nixon?
那不是尼克森上尉吗?
I think so.
我想是的
What the hell's he doing in his harness?
他带着伞具做什么?
I don't know.
不知道
Maybe we jumped into Berlin, the war's over.
也许我们跳伞到了柏林 战争就已经结束了
So, what happened?
结果怎么样?
No dice with the Fraulein?
没泡到德国小妞?
No dice. She smacked me in the mouth.
她赏了我一巴掌
Tell you what, though.
虽然这样
Germany's looking to be pretty good fraternizing territory, huh?
我觉得德国看来会变成蛮亲善的地方
Did you lose your cigarettes?
你的香烟呢?
Oh, God.
上帝啊
God, ja, ja, ja.
上帝
Hold up, hold up, hold up.
等等
That's right, yeah.
没错 就是这样 太棒了
Janovec!
杰诺维克!
Oh, shit!
糟了!
Sir.
长官
Where's my stuff?
我的东西呢?
I thought I'd leave it over there, sir.
我把它放在那边了 长官
Over there.
那边
Here.
往这儿走
Thanks.
多谢
You're welcome, sir.
不客气 长官
Oh, sir.
长官
'Morning, sir.
早上好 长官
'Morning.
早
You got a box all this stuff will fit into?
你有可以放的下这些东西的箱子吗?
Yes, sir, I think so, same destination?
我想有的 长官 一样的目的地?
Yeah.
是的
Yes, sir, I'll make sure it goes out first thing in the morning.
好的 长官我会确定它明早第一时间寄出去
Thank you, Private.
谢谢你
Your folks are gonna have quite a collection by the time you get...
我确定你们这些人都能搜集到一堆东西...
...home, sir.
...带回家 长官
Finders keepers.
谁找到的就是谁的
Yes, sir.
是的 长官
Nix?
尼克?
In here.
在这里
Dog.
你这混蛋
Making combat jumps with the 17th while I'm in supply briefings all morning.
当我整早在做补给简报的时候 你却跟第17师进行空降作战?
Yeah, lucky me.
对 算我好运
No, congratulations.
恭喜你
You're probably the only man in the 101st with three combat stars over his jump wings.
你可能是101师中唯一在伞徽上能别上三颗作战星星的人
Not bad for someone who's never fired his weapon in combat?
对一个从未在战斗中开过一枪的人来说 不算太坏吧?
Really?
真的吗?
Really, you've never...
你真的从来没...
No.
没有
Not even with all the action we've seen?
在我们经历过的那么多战役中?
Not a round.
一枪都没有
So...
那么...
How'd it go this morning, the jump?
你今天早上跳的如何?
It was great, fantastic.
真不错 棒极了!
We took a direct hit over the drop zone.
我们在空投区直接被命中
I got out. Two others got out.
我跳出来了 另外两个也跳了
The rest of the boys?
其他的弟兄呢?
Well, they blew up over Germany somewhere.
他们在德国上空某处爆炸了
Yeah, I'm sorry.
我很遗憾...
About what?
关于什么?
Well, tough situation for the...
这个惨烈的状况发生在...
Oh, yeah, the boys, yeah.
对...那些兄弟
It's terrible.
真是可怕
Oh, well, wasn't me.
还好不是我
You know, the real tragedy is they also lost their CO.
你知道吗 真正惨的是他们的连长也死了
So guess who gets to write all the letters home.
所以猜猜看谁该帮他们写信回家?
Goddamn nightmare.
真是个噩梦
Got a visit from Colonel Sink this morning.
今早辛克上校来过
And how is the good colonel?
这位好上校如何?
Concerned.
很关切
Still drinking nothing but the Vat 69?
你还是只喝"翡特69"的陈年威士忌吗?
Only the finest for Mrs. Nixon's baby boy.
尼克森太太的宝贝儿子只喝最好的酒
Had a problem up at regiment?
与团部闹的不愉快吗?
What, this?
这个吗?
Is that what he said?
他是这么跟你说的吗?
No, I just don't like it up there.
没有 我只是不喜欢那里而已
Good,
很好!
so you'll be happy to hear that Sink is transferring you back down to Battalion S-3.
那你应该很高兴听到辛克上校要把你降回营部作战官
What do you think I should write to these parents, Dick?
你觉得我该写些什么 给这些父母 迪克?
Hear what I said, Nix? You've been demoted.
你听到我的话了吗 尼克? 你被降级了...
Yeah, demoted, got you.
对 降级 知道了!
I don't know how to tell them...
因为我不知道该怎么告诉他们
...their kids never even got out of the plane.
他们的孩子甚至连跳都来不及跳
You tell them what you always tell them:
告诉他们你一向告诉他们的
"Their sons died as heroes."
"他们的儿子英勇阵亡"
You really still believe that?
你还相信那一套?
Yeah, I do.
是 我相信
Don't you?
你不信吗?
"The Cooperative for American Remittance to Europe...
美国人汇寄协助欧洲行动
"...or CARE, has begun assembling food packages stateside...
简称为CARE 已经开始在美国本土聚集食品
"...to assist those European families in dire need."
来帮助那些有迫切需要的欧洲家庭
Which is presumably all of them.
讲起来所有家庭都算是
So, notes home to your family reminding them...
所以感谢你们写信回家
...to donate whatever they can would be much appreciated.
提醒他们尽可能的捐款
I'm sure that you'll be happy to know...
我确定你们会很高兴知道
...Oklahoma's still playing on Broadway.
"奥克拉荷马"还在百老汇上演
"Oklahoma where the wind comes sweepin' down the plain
∮奥克拉荷马的微风吹抚着平原∮
"And the wavin' wheat can sure smell sweet
∮波浪般的麦穗 闻起来多香甜∮
"When the wind comes
∮当阵阵和风∮
"Right behind the rain"
∮在雨后出现∮
O'Keefe, you were sitting on your bayonet there?
欧基夫 你坐到刺刀了?
Why don't you leave the singing to Luz?
你还是让鲁兹来唱好了
Hey, unless you wanna do...
除非你想表演一段歌舞秀
...Surrey with the Fringe on Top, O'Keefe.
欧基夫 给你选一样
Rita Hayworth's getting married.
丽塔海华丝要结婚了
Oh, Rita, say it isn't true.
丽塔 告诉我这不是真的
Abbott and Costello...
劳莱和哈台...
Wartime news.
战地新闻
"Resistance in the Rhur pocket's crumbling.
在鲁尔区的反抗瓦解了
"It looks like there might be a breakout in Remagen."
看来在雷玛根将有所突破
Apparently the Krauts forgot to blow up a bridge when they headed back over the Rhine.
显然德军在从战线撤走时忘了炸掉其中一座桥
I guess the boys in the 17th Airborne did okay after all.
我想第17空降师的弟兄最后战果还不错
Forget it, we'd be in Berlin by now, sir...
别提了 要不现在早就攻下柏林了
...if it was us instead of them?
如果是换我们去的话
That's right!
没错 对!
When do you think we'll jump into Berlin...
你觉得我们何时才会跳伞到柏林
...see some real action?
见识下真正的战斗?
You in a rush?
你赶时问吗?
No.
不是
So, you wanna go home with a Congressional Medal of Honor?
你是不是想捧个国会荣誉勋章回去还是怎么样?
I just thought I'd ask.
没有 我只是想我该问问
Well, why don't you do us all a favor?
那麻烦你帮个忙
Don't think.
什么也别想
Damn replacements.
该死的新兵
Hallelujah.
哈利路亚
'Bout time.
也该是时候了
Yeah, consider yourselves lucky.
你们应该感到幸运的
Nixon was giving another current events lecture.
尼克森在发表"当代大事"的演说
So, tell me nothing's happening.
告诉我你们这儿风平浪静
Nothing's happening.
风平浪静
Couple of artillery rounds at dawn...
在黎明有几发炮击
...probably from across the river, but...
可能是从河对岸打过来的
...that's about it.
就这样而已
It spooked Hashey, though.
只是吓了赫胥一跳
Here, Perco, I just finished it.
给你 派康提 我刚读完
Oh, yeah? Any sex in it?
是吗? 有没有关于性的情节?
Ain't that kind of book.
不是那种书
- See you. - Yeah, see you.
- 回见! - 好 再见!
Okay, move on.
好 继续前进
Hey, O'Brien.
嘿 欧布安
Relax, would you? I'm trying to read.
轻点 好吗? 我要看书
It's O'Keefe.
我叫欧基夫
Is that right?
是吗?
Yeah, Patrick O'Keefe.
对 帕特里克·欧基夫
My friends call me Paddy.
我的朋友叫我派弟
Hey, O'Brien.
嘿 欧布安
Shut up!
闭嘴!
I told you, it's O'Keefe.
我说过我叫欧基夫
Do you know why no one remembers your name?
你知道为什么没有人记得你的名字?
It's 'cause no one wants to remember your name.
那是因为没有人想要去记你的名字
There's too many Smiths, Dimattos and O'Keefes...
有太多的史密斯...迪马拖...欧基夫...
...and O'Briens, who show up here replacing Toccoa men...
欧布安...来补充托卡尔老爹
...that you replacements got killed in the first place.
结果你们这些笨新兵先阵亡
And they're all like you. They're all piss and vinegar.
他们都跟你一样笨手笨脚的
"Where are the Krauts at?"
"德军在哪儿? "
"Let me at them."
"让我来对付他们"
"When will I get to jump into Berlin?"
"我什么时候会跳伞到柏林? "
Two days later, there they are...
两天之后 他们倒在地上
...with their guts hanging out...
肚破肠流
...and they're screaming for a medic.
声嘶力竭的叫医护兵
Begging for their goddamn mother.
哭爹喊娘的
Them dumb fucks don't even know they're dead yet.
那些笨蛋连他们已经死了都还不知道呢
Hey, are you listening to me?
你有在听我说吗?
Do you get that this is the best part of fucking war I've seen?
你知道 这段时期是我在战争中看过最好的部分吗?
I got hot chow, hot showers, warm bed.
我有热餐吃...热水洗...暖和的床!
Germany is almost as good as being home.
在德国几乎跟在家一样好
I even got to wipe my ass with real toilet paper today.
我今天甚至可以用真的卫生纸擦屁股
Quit asking about when you're gonna see some action, will you?
所以别再问你什么时候可以见识到战斗 好吗?
And stop with the fucking love songs!
别再唱那首该死的情歌!
When'd you ship out?
你何时离家的?
A few weeks ago?
几个星期前?
Yeah.
对
It's been two years since I seen home.
我离家已经两年了
Two years.
两年了
This fucking war.
这该死的战争
Neither patrol found a single Kraut.
两次巡逻都没发现德军
There were none here either.
这里也没有
They'll be across the river by now.
他们现在应该在河对岸
Let's send out a night patrol.
让我们派出一支夜巡队
Check out the embankment on the far side.
查看下另一头的堤岸
President's dead.
总统去世了
Pair of queens bets.
两对Q说话
All right, two bucks.
好 赌两块
Nix.
尼克
No, I'm out.
不 我不跟了
All right.
好吧
Well, I'll call you two...
我跟你
...and I'll raise you another two.
再加两块
I can't believe we're not gonna drop into Berlin.
我不信我们不跳伞到柏林了
No shit.
没错
Ike's gonna let the Russkies have it.
艾森豪威尔要让俄国佬占领它
Russkies.
俄国佬
God damn it.
他妈的
Let me tell you something:
我跟你说吧：
This war is not about fighting anymore.
这场战争已经无关战斗了
It's about who gets what.
现在是看谁占领了什么
Why don't you deal me out of the next hand?
你们下一把再发牌给我
What about your money?
你的钱呢?
Are we waiting on him again?
我们又要等他吗?
Yep.
对
Goddamn drugstore.
该死的杂货店
Sir.
长官
Hey, guys, wait up.
嘿 伙计 等一下
Hey, Dexter, how you doing?
嘿 戴克斯特 你好吗?
Good to see you.
很高兴见到你
You know who that was?
知道那是谁吗?
No.
不知道
'Morning.
早安
Captain Nixon.
尼克森上尉
Good to see you, sir.
很高兴见到你 长官
I think I have some mail for you.
我想我这儿有你的信
Yeah, I was gonna drop it off this afternoon...
我本来想下午...
...with all the other 2nd Battalion mail.
跟第二营其他的信一起给你
But since you're here...
可是既然你来了
Thanks.
谢谢
Listen, I'm having some trouble finding some whiskey.
我跟你说 我找不到威士忌
Whiskey?
威士忌?
Yeah, a particular brand of whiskey.
对 一种特别的牌子
Vat 69.
翡特69
Exactly right.
完全正确
I gotta be honest, sir...
老实说 长官
...that ain't gonna be easy to find in Germany.
那个牌子在德国很难找到
Pickings are kind of slim here.
这里的选择不多
Yeah, don't I know it?
对 这我知道
And even if I do find some, sir...
还有如果我真的找到几瓶 长官
...it ain't gonna be cheap.
它恐怕并不便宜
That won't be a problem.
钱不是问题
Hey, you hear the news?
魏斯特 你听到消息了吗?
Sorry, sir. I didn't realize that you were here.
抱歉 长官 我不知道你在这儿
What news?
什么消息?
300,000 Krauts just surrendered.
三十万德军刚刚投降了
Three hundred?
三十万?
Yeah, we're moving out in an hour.
对 我们一小时内要出发
- One hour? - Yeah
- 一小时? - 是的
Sir, sir.
长官
Your mail.
你的信
Keep looking.
继续帮我找
Excuse me, pardon me.
对不起
Get a move on, let's go.
要出发了 我们走
Jesus Christ, the dog?
老天 连那只狗?
Lew?
路易?
Cathy's divorcing me.
凯西要跟我离婚
I'm sorry.
我很遗憾
She's taking everything.
她要拿走所有的东西
She's taking the house...
她要拿走房子
...taking the kid.
带走孩子
She's taking the dog.
还要把狗带走
It's not even her dog!
那根本不是她的狗!
It's my dog!
那是我的狗!
She's taking my dog!
她要带走我的狗!
Let's go, load them up, come on!
我们走 把它们装好 走吧!
Sarge, what do you have in here?
中士 你们这里有什么?
Germans?
德国人吗?
Hey, Perconte.
派康提
You got a lighter?
你有打火机吗?
No, sir, I don't smoke.
没有 长官 我不抽烟
Hey, where we headed?
嘿 我们要去哪里?
To the Alps. Let me see that lighter.
我们要上阿尔卑斯山 打火机给我
- The Alps? - Yeah.
- 阿尔卑斯山? - 对!
- That near Berlin, sir? - No.
- 它在柏林附近吗? - 不是
That's in Bavaria.
那是在巴伐利亚
Birthplace of national socialism.
国家社会主义(即纳粹)党的发源地
So, that mean no drop into Berlin?
这意思是我们不会跳伞进柏林了?
No drop into Berlin.
不会了
Hitler ordered the Waffen SS to hide in the mountains and repel all invaders.
希特勒下令 叫武装党卫军在山区藏洞来驱逐侵略者
He wants them to start a guerrilla war.
他要他们开始进行本土保卫战
Invaders.
侵略者
Damn, I like the sound of that.
听起来挺好的
They'll die the last man trying.
他们要战到最后一兵一卒
- Sir. - What?
- 长官 - 什么事?
My lighter.
我的打火机
All right, nice lighter.
好吧 打火机不错
Thanks.
谢谢
Waffen SS?
武装党卫军?
Looks like you'll get your wish anyway, O'Flannery.
看来你的愿望要实现了 欧佛拉内
Those guys...
那些人...
Fucking crazy.
根本是疯子
It's O'Keefe.
我叫欧基夫
"He ain't gonna jump no more
∮他不需要再跳了∮
"Gory, gory, what a hell of a way to die
∮碧血如泉 取义成仁∮
"Risers wrapped around his neck Connectors cracked his dome
∮基督缠绕着他的颈部∮
"Suspension lines were tied in knots Around his skinny bones
∮围着他的棱骨∮
"The canopy became the shroud he hurdled to the ground
∮以天空为幕 他冲向地表∮
"He ain't gonna jump no more
∮他不需要再跳了∮
"Gory, gory, what a hell of a way to die
∮碧血如泉 取义成仁∮
You okay, Nix?
你还好吗 尼克?
Yeah, I'm fine.
好 我很好
"He ain't gonna jump no more"
∮他不需要再跳了∮
She hates that dog.
她痛恨那只狗
"His blood went spurting high
∮他血流如注∮
"His comrades they were heard to say, 'A hell of a way to die'
∮他以为自己绝不会取义成仁∮
"He laid there rolling 'round in the welter of his gore
∮他躺在自己的血泊中∮
"He ain't gonna jump no more
∮他不用再跳了∮
"Gory, gory, what a hell of a way to die
∮碧血如泉 取义成仁∮
There's gonna be good times, Web.
好日子快要来了 韦伯
When we get home, I mean.
我是说在我们回家之后
First thing I'm gonna do...
我第一件要做的事
...is get my job back at the cab company in Frisco.
是到旧金山找回在出租车公司的工作
Make a killing off all those sailors coming home, you know?
赚爆那些返乡水兵的钱
Then I'm gonna find me a nice Jewish girl...
然后我要找个好犹太女孩
...with great big, soft titties...
有超大酥胸
...and a smile to die for.
还有迷人笑容的那种
Marry her.
把她娶回家
Then I'm gonna buy a house...
然后我要买栋房子
...a big house with lots of bedrooms...
一间有很多房间的大房子
...for all the little Liebgotts we're gonna be making.
让我们能生一群小李高特
She ought to like that.
她一定会喜欢的
Hey, Janovec, what you reading?
杰诺维克 你在看什么?
An article.
一篇文章
No shit.
真的?
What's it about?
有关什么的?
It's about why we're fighting the war.
关于我们为何而战
Why are we fighting the war, Janovec?
我们为何而战 杰诺维克?
It seems that the Germans are bad.
看来好象是德国人很坏
Very bad.
非常坏
You don't say.
还用你说
The Germans are bad?
德国人很坏 不是吗?
Hey, Frank, this guy's reading an article over here.
嘿 法兰克 这家伙在读的文章
It says the Germans are bad.
说德国人很坏
So, what about you, Web?
那你呢 韦伯?
You learn something new every day?
每天都学到新事物 对吧?
I guess I'll finish school first and then...
我要先完成学业 然后...
Wait a minute, finish school?
等一下 完成学业?
You mean all this time you've been talking about Harvard this...
你是说你老是哈佛长哈佛短的
...and Harvard that, and you ain't even finished?
结果你根本没毕业?
For one thing I haven't told you anything.
我只有这件事没提
Yes, yes, I haven't finished.
对 我是没有毕业
So the fuck what?
那又怎样?
All right, Web, breathe a little. Jesus.
好 我们暂时别谈这个话题
Fuck.
见鬼
It's just the way you always talked, you know?
因为你老是讲的好象是 你知道
We all figured that...
我们都以为...
Hey, you know, you're right.
你知道吗? 你说的对
So the fuck what?
没毕业又怎样?
So, what did you study?
那你念的是什么?
Literature.
文学
Get out of here.
别开玩笑了
You serious?
真的吗?
I love to read.
我也爱看书
Do you?
是吗?
Dick Tracy, Flash Gordon mostly.
迪克崔西 闪电侠
Yeah, fuck.
对 又怎样呢?
Tell her she's got five minutes.
告诉她她只有五分钟
Raus, raus.
出去 出去
Sir, she says they've got nowhere to go...
长官 她说她们无处可去
...but the house next door is...
而隔壁又是...
Hey, hey, do you hear this?
嘿 你们听到了吗?
He says he ain't a Nazi.
这家伙说他不是纳粹
Why haven't I met a Nazi yet in all of Germany?
为什么我到了德国却还没遇上一个纳粹?
We're only gonna be here one night.
我们只在这儿待一晚
You've got four minutes.
你还有四分钟
Raus.
出去
Come on.
快点
Let's go. Move!
快走!
All of you, out!
都出去!
Look at them.
你看他们
Even in defeat, they still know how to march with pride.
就算是战败了 他们还是带着傲气行军
Hey, you!
嘿 你!
That's right, you stupid Kraut bastards!
没错 就是你这个笨德国杂种!
That's right!
没错!
Say hello to Ford and General fucking Motors.
跟福特和通用汽车问好
You stupid fascist pigs.
你们这群笨法西斯猪
Look at you!
看看你们!
You have horses.
你们只有马
What were you thinking?
你们是怎么想的?
That's enough, Webster.
够了 韦伯斯特
Give it a rest.
别再说了
Dragging our asses half-way around the world...
把我们从半个地球外拖来
...interrupting our lives.
干扰我们的生活
For what?
为了什么?
You ignorant, servile scum!
你们这些无知 卑贱的人渣!
What the fuck are we doing here?
我们在这里干什么?
I wanna send out some patrols.
我要派出一些巡逻队
We'll have Dog here in the village. Easy and Fox in the woods.
Ｄ连搜索村庄 Ｅ连和Ｆ连搜索树林
Easy Company's gonna take the northwest. Lt. Lipton...
Ｅ连负责西北区 李普少尉
Sir.
长官!
Have 1st and 2nd Platoons go to the woods.
叫第一、第二排进森林扫荡
Have 3rd swing around.
叫第三排在外围扫荡
Yes, sir. 1st Sergeant Talbert.
是的 长官 泰伯特军士长
You're not worried about an ambush, are you?
你不是担心伏击吧?
No.
不
Just in case we have to stay here for the night.
只是因为我们有可能在这里过夜
- O'Keefe. - Sarge
- 欧基夫 - 中士
Why the hell are you so jumpy, boy?
你为什么那么紧张 小子?
I'm not jumpy.
我没有紧张
I'm fine.
我很好
Can hear your heart pounding in Arkansas, boy.
我大老远就可以听见你的心跳 小子
Jesus Christ, give the kid a break, Bull.
你别再逗他了 大牛
Hey, George.
乔治
Yeah?
什么?
Does this kind of remind you of Bastogne?
这有没有让你想起巴斯通?
Yeah, now that you mention it.
有 你说我才想起来
Except, of course, there's no snow...
除了这里没有雪
...we got warm grub in our bellies...
我们有热餐吃
...and the trees aren't fucking exploding from Kraut artillery.
而且树干没被老德轰的七零八落
But, yeah, Frank, other than that...
对! 法兰克 除此之外...
...it's a lot like Bastogne.
这里很象巴斯通
Right.
对
Bull, smack him for me, please.
大牛 帮我赏他一巴掌
Thank you.
谢谢你
Hello?
有人吗?
It sure is quiet.
这里真是安静
He is right, fellows.
他说的对 各位
- You seen Foley? - No.
- 看到佛利没有? - 没有!
Hey, guys.
嘿 伙计
Any of you see any of the officers?
有人看到任何军官吗?
- No, speak to Popeye. - Hey Pop.
- 没有 去问问普派 - 嘿 普派
Popeye, you seen any officers? Nixon, Foley?
普派 你看到哪个军官吗? 尼克森? 佛利?
Speirs is searching them buildings right down the street.
史毕尔在沿街搜索建筑物
What's the matter?
什么事?
More, have you seen any of the officers?
摩尔 你有看到任何军官吗?
Yeah, Major Winters is right in there.
有 温特斯少校就在里面
Are you all right, Frank?
你还好吗 法兰克?
Major Winters, sir.
温特斯少校 长官
We found something.
我们发现了些东西
We're out on patrol and we came across this...
我们在执行巡逻任务 然后 我们发现了这个...
What, what, what? Frank, Frank, what is it?
什么...? 法兰克 发现了什么?
I don't know, sir.
我不知道 长官
I don't know.
我不知道
Major, sir.
少校
Open it up.
把它打开
Yes, sir.
是 长官
Stand back.
退后
Give us some room here, stand back.
给我们一点空间 退后一点
Christenson, any of your men speak German?
克里斯登生 你手下谁会说德语?
No, sir.
没有 长官
I need Liebgott. Liebgott!
我需要李高特! 李高特!
Lipton, find me Liebgott.
李普 去找李高特
Yes, sir.
是 长官
Liebgott, Liebgott!
李高特!
Major needs you up front, right now.
少校要你到前面来 马上!
Sure.
是 长官
All right, boys.
好了 小伙子们
These people need care.
这些人需要照顾
Give them water and all spare rations.
给他们水喝 还有多的口粮
Grab me some blankets, quick.
去拿些毛毯来 快去!
Oh, my God.
我的上帝啊
Dick?
迪克?
I'm sorry.
很抱歉
Here, take some water.
拿去 喝点水
Jesus, Web, can you believe this place?
老天 韦伯 你相信有这种地方吗?
No.
不相信
It's okay.
没事了
Better now.
现在好了
He said the guards left this morning, sir.
他说守卫今早刚离开 长官
They burned some of the huts first...
他们先放火烧了些木屋
...with the prisoners still in them, sir alive.
犯人都还在屋里 长官 活生生的...被烧死
Jesus Christ.
我的老天
Some of the prisoners tried to stop them.
有些犯人想要阻止他们
Some of them were killed.
有人就被杀了
They didn't have enough ammo for all the prisoners, so...
他们没有足够子弹杀光所有的犯人
...they killed as many as they could...
所以他们就尽量的杀
...before they left the camp.
在他们离开集中营之前
They locked the gates behind them and headed south.
他们把大门锁上 朝南边走了
Someone in town must have told them we were coming.
镇上一定有人跟他们说我们来了
Yeah, I think so.
对 我也这么想
Will you ask him...
麻烦你问他...
...ask him what kind of camp this is?
问他这是什么样的营区?
What...
什么...
Why are they here?
为什么他们在这里?
He says it's a work camp for...
他说这是一个劳改集中营
Unerwunscht?
专门关押 Unerwunscht?
I'm not sure what the word means, sir.
我不确定这个字的意思 长官
Unwanted, disliked maybe?
也许是不需要 不喜欢?
Criminals?
罪犯?
I don't think criminals, sir.
我想不是罪犯的意思 长官
No.
不是
Doctors, musicians.
有医生 音乐家...
Tailors, clerks. Farmers, intellectuals. I mean, normal people.
裁缝、职员、农夫、知识分子 我的意思是 普通老百姓
Juden, Juden.
犹太人
They're Jews.
他们是犹太人
Poles and gypsies.
波兰人跟吉普赛人
Liebgott?
李高特?
The women's camp is at the next railroad stop.
妇女集中营在下一个火车站
Hey, Babe, come here.
嘿 贝比 过来这里
Look at their arms.
看他们的手臂
Like cattle.
跟牲口一样
Goddamn.
可恶
Ah, Jesus.
老天爷
O'Keefe?
欧基夫?
I'm gonna call Sink.
我要打电话给辛克上校
Find Speirs and figure out how the hell to get them some food...
叫史毕尔想办法给他们弄些食物...
...and water.
还有水
Let's go, let's pick up the pace, come on.
我们走 速度加快点
Sergeant Martin...
马丁中士
...get what fits on the deuce and a half.
把能装上小卡车的想办法弄来
Move, let's move.
快 我们走!
Shut up.
闭嘴
Take everything, take it all.
把所有东西都拿走
Check the back and shut up!
到后面看看...闭嘴!
Check the back and see if there's any kind of...
到后面看看还有没有东西可以...
Shut up!
闭嘴!
I said shut up, you Nazi fuck!
我叫你闭嘴 你这个纳粹王八蛋!
You're not a Nazi?
你不是纳粹?
My mistake, you fat fucking prick.
那是我搞错了? 你这个死肥走狗?
How about a human being? Are you one of those?
那人呢? 你算是人吗?
Or will you tell me you never smelled the fucking stench?
或者是你要告诉我 你从没闻到那股尸臭味?
Let him go, Web.
放了他
He says he doesn't know what the hell you're talking about.
他说他听不懂你在说什么
Bullshit.
狗屁
Sergeant Talbert, this is chaos.
泰伯特军士长 这真是混乱
There's plenty to go around, please.
别急 每一个人都有份
We've got more water on the way.
还有更多的水会送来
Dick, Major Winters.
迪克! 温特斯少校
Yes, sir.
是 长官
Sir.
长官
This is Doctor Kent, the regimental surgeon.
这位是肯特医官 团部的外科大夫
Doc, tell Major Winters and Captain Nixon what you just told me.
医生 把你刚告诉我的 去告诉温特斯少校和尼克森上尉
Yes, sir. We need to stop giving these men food right now.
我们得立刻停止供应这些人食物
They're starving.
他们处于饥饿状态
If they eat too much too quickly...
如果我们太快给他们吃太多东西
...they'll eat themselves to death.
反而会导致他们死亡
We need to keep them here...
我们需要将他们留在营内
...till we can find a place for them in town.
直到在镇上找到他们栖身之处
You want us to lock these people back up?
你要我们把这些人再关回去?
We got no choice, Nix.
我们别无选择 尼克
Otherwise they might scatter.
不然他们会四处分散
We must keep them centralized...
我们需要将他们集中起来
...to supervise their food intake and medical treatment.
以便监督他们的食物摄取跟医疗
So, until we find some place better...
所以在我们找到更好的地方之前
Colonel Sink.
辛克上校
It's a crying ass shame, but let's get it done.
这真是不得已的 就这么办吧
Yes, sir.
是 长官
I don't like it any more than you guys.
我跟你们一样不愿意
General Taylor?
泰勒将军?
Bob Sink, 506.
我是506团的鲍伯·辛克
Sir, we're on, we're at Landsberg...
长官 我们在...蓝德斯堡
...the other side of Buchloe.
布克洛的另一头
We found something I believe you ought to see, sir.
我们发现了些你应该要来看看的东西 长官
I can't tell them that, sir.
我没有办法跟他们说 长官
You've got to, Joe.
非说不可 乔
Yes, sir.
好吧 长官
Grant, Christenson.
格兰特 克里斯登生
The prisoners must be put back in the camp immediately.
这些人犯必须马上回集中营
Let the men know.
去告诉大家
Turns out I'm staying in the only dry frigging house in Germany.
搞了半天 结果我住在全德国唯一没有酒喝的房子
Thought you weren't drinking the local.
我还以为你不喝当地的酒
Yeah, well.
管他的
Heard from Division.
我听到师部发来的消息
Been finding camps like this all over the place.
到处不断发现象这样的集中营
Jesus.
老天
Seems the Russians liberated one a lot worse.
俄国人好象找到一个更悲惨的
Worse?
更惨?
Yeah.
对
Apparently.
似乎是这样
Ten times as big.
比这个还大上十倍
Execution chambers, ovens.
有毒气室 火炉
For cremating all the bodies.
是用来焚化尸体的
Jesus.
老天啊
The locals claim that they never even knew the camp existed.
当地居民都说他们从不知道集中营的存在
They say we're exaggerating.
他们都说我们太夸张了
Well, they're gonna have a hell of an education tomorrow.
明天他们就要来个震撼教育
General Taylor declared martial law about an hour ago.
泰勒将军大约在一小时前宣布了戒严令
Ordered every able-bodied German in town aged 14 to 80, to start burying the bodies.
命令全镇年龄14到80岁之间的健康镇民开始帮忙埋葬尸体
That'll begin in the morning.
明天早上开始
10th Armored are gonna supervise cleanup.
第十装甲师会监督清理工作
What about us?
那我们呢?
We head out for Thalheim, Thalheim, tomorrow.
我们向达兰...塔兰出发
1200 hours.
明天中午十二点
Kerchief, sir?
要不要手帕 长官?
What?
什么?
No, thanks.
不用了 谢谢
Move along.
向前移
Over there.
放到那里
Don't stop. Keep digging.
别停 继续挖
You, too. Come on.
你们俩 快点
Hitler's dead.
希特勒死了
Holy shit.
天啊
Shot himself in Berlin.
在柏林举枪自尽了
Is the war over, sir?
战争结束了吗 长官?
No.
还没有
We have orders to Berchtesgaden.
我们奉命前往贝希特斯佳登
We're gonna move out in one hour.
一个小时内出发
Why, the man's not home?
为什么? 主人不是死了吗?
Should've killed himself three years ago.
他三年前就该自杀了
Saved us a lot of trouble.
那就会省我们许多麻烦
Yeah, he should've...
对 他早该如此...
...but he didn't.
可惜他没有